Oh, you got to really get it up in there, dawg.
把我弄爽点 老兄
Some sins deserve eternal damnation.
有些罪孽应该受到永恒的诅咒
I've committed murders.
我犯下了谋杀罪
Inmate refused visitation.
囚犯拒绝探视
No!
不!
A panic attack. Whatever you're doing, stop it.
是惊恐发作 不管你在做什么 停下来
They killed Cameron Coleman because
他们杀了卡梅隆科尔曼
they thought that he was the fucking leak. I'm done.
因为他们认为他是泄密者 我受够了
Cameron Coleman wasn't the leak.
卡梅隆科尔曼并不是泄密者
So, either Sage was lying to you,
所以 要么智者在骗你
or she's as useless as tits on a mouse.
要么她就像老鼠的乳头一样毫无用处
I'd do anything for you.
我愿意为您做任何事
That's my boy.
我的乖男孩
I hate you.
我恨你
Kimiko!
喜美子
Victoria here, she's an integral part of the plan.
维多利亚是这个计划中 不可或缺的一部分
We'll handle Singer after the election's certified.
我们将在选举被获准后处理辛格尔
We need plausible deniability when the 25th is invoked.
第二十五项法案被实施时 你需要合理的推诿
You're talking about a coup.
你说的可是一场政变啊
You give us a list of what you need to extract the virus, and make it
列出一份清单 告诉我们提取病毒都需要什么
strong enough to top Homelander.
提高病毒的强度 足以杀掉祖国人才行
We're not just talking about killing Homelander,
我们说的不是杀死祖国人而已
we're talking about killing every Supe on Earth.
而是杀掉地球上的每一个超人类
No one ever said nothing about genocide.
没人说过要搞种族灭绝
What the fuck's that supposed to mean, "you're me"?
这他妈的是什么意思 你就是我?
You got a big old fat V'd-up brain tumor, you cunt,
注射过五号之后 你的大脑里 长出了一个大大的肿瘤 你个混蛋
which is why you are seeing me in the first place.
所以你才看得到我!
I am you.
我就是你
Well, Merry Christmas, A-Train!
圣诞快乐 火车头!
Oh, Merry Christmas, Ryan.
圣诞快乐 莱恩
Why the long face?
为什么不开心?
Antifa.
反法西斯行动
What's that?
那是什么?
Well, Ryan, it's a word for people
莱恩 这个词形容
who hate superheroes and America
讨厌超级英雄和美国
even more than they hate Christmas.
甚于讨厌圣诞节的人
Well, what do they look like?
他们长什么样?
That's the problem. They can look like anyone,
那就是问题所在 他们可能是任何人
your neighbors, your teachers, even your mom and dad.
你的邻居 你的老师 甚至你的爸妈
Uh, Tommy, can we cut out for a second?Uh, that's a cut on rehearsal.
汤米 可以暂停一下吗?暂停排练
That's a cut.
停好
Back in 20, everyone.
各位 休息20分钟
Hey, is everything okay?
没什么事吧?
I mean, yeah, it's just...
让孩子们去举报自己的父母 这也
we're telling kids to report on their own parents.
你爸已经批准这些歌词了
The lyrics were approved by your dad. Personally, so...
亲自批准的 所以
Right. Right, yeah, yeah.
对哦 是哈 对
Right.Yeah. It's no problem.
对 没问题
I just need to go 10-1.
我得去趟洗手间
Yeah.
好
PR made that apology to Temple Beth El,
公关部向犹太教会道歉了
so that should be a done fucking deal.
所以这事已经板上钉钉了
Um, secondly, we've got a...
其次 我们有个很好的
I thought the meeting started at 11:00.
不是11点开会吗?
We moved it up.
我们提前开了
Um, next.
下一项
Oh, marketing would like to start selling these NFTs of you.
营销部想开始出售你的非同质化代币
Apparently, you're not just buying JPEGs, you're joining a community.
显然 买家不只是购买图片文件 还会加入虚拟社区
Ashley.Yes, sir?
艾诗丽是 先生
Get out.Yes, sir.
出去是 先生
Sorry, sir. Yes, absolutely.
对不起 先生 是 没问题
Sage...
智者
who's the leak?
泄密者是谁?
We're making inquiries.
我们正在调查
It's a process, we're eliminating...
需要花点时间 我们需要
I assume you know what that is.
我想你很清楚这是什么
It's a bug.Specifically William Butcher's bug.
是监听器 威廉布彻尔布下的监听器
They probably heard every single word we said at Tek-Knight's.
我们在泰克骑士庄园说的每一个字 他们可能都听到了
And likely killed him.
很可能还杀了他
They won't go public with the information.
他们不会公开这些信息
And why not?Because it would short-circuit
为什么呢?因为会妨碍
everything they really want,
他们得到自己想要的东西
which is to quietly take out Neuman once and for all.
他们想一劳永逸地 神不知鬼不觉地除掉纽曼
We should slaughter Butcher and his whole fucking team.
我们应该把布彻尔及其整个团队 都杀个片甲不留
Now that is a great idea, sir.
真是个好主意 先生
Butcher will be dead in a few months anyway.
反正布彻尔也活不了几个月了
And this close to go-time, I wouldn't stir up shit with the CIA.
就要实行大计划了 我可不想引起中情局的注意
Yes, yes, yes. Your illustrious fucking plan.
是的!你那该死的杰出计划
We killed Cameron Coleman for no reason.
我们无缘无故地杀了卡梅隆科尔曼
A speed bump but, ultimately, harmless.
暂时的困难 但无碍于计划
Cameron golfed with Mike Lindell,
卡梅隆和迈克林德尔一起打高尔夫球
who just pulled 50 million bucks worth of pillow commercials.
后者撤走了 价值五千万美元的枕头广告投资
You call that harmless?
那叫无碍吗?
Oh, look at Daisy Duck Dynasty doing math.
看看是谁在赶鸭子上架做算数呢
You know, Firecracker and I have been talking.
我和鞭炮讨论来着
Stimulating, I'm sure.
肯定相当刺激
Sorry.
对不起
You have brains, Sage,
你有头脑 智者
but I have wisdom.
但我有智慧
And what happens if those brains of yours
如果你的大脑再次受伤
get blown out again, leaving you
让你像个胡言乱语的白痴
talking like a gibbering idiot?
那该怎么办?
Firecracker and I will find the leak.
我和鞭炮会找出泄密者
With respect, the last time...
恕我直言 上次
Respect? I don't hear no fucking respect.
宽恕你?我没感觉你在寻求宽恕
In fact, I am personally offended
事实上 你对这位伟大人物这么讲话
by the way you are talking to this great man.
令我个人感到极受冒犯
You just focus on the shooter,
你专心管好枪手就行了
make sure he's good to go on the sixth.
确保他六号那天准备就绪
He'll be ready.
他会准备好的
Good.
好的
You may leave.
你可以离开了
This one's called The World's Our Oyster.
这首叫《世界是我们的牡蛎》
"Shimmering forests of kelp
闪闪发光的海带森林
Like nature's car wash brushes
就像大自然的洗车刷
At the dark bottom, jellyfish glow
在黑暗的海底 水母发光
Like frat house lava lamps
就像兄弟会的熔岩灯
I can swim you anywhere
我可以带你游去任何地方
The seven seas, one big wet road."
七大洋 水路长长
Jesus, Kevin.
天哪 凯文
You really have the soul of a poet.
你确实有着诗人的灵魂
Stop.
好啦
You're so bad.
你真坏
And, God, your tongue
天哪 你的舌头
is like an outboard motor.Yeah?
就像舷外发动机 是吗?
I came so many times.
我高潮了好多次
Really?
真的吗?
I, uh, I got to go, babe.
我 我得走了 宝贝
What? You do?
什么?这就走?
Duty calls.
职责在身
Wait. No, no. Wait.
等等 不 等等!
Come on, babe. You know you can't be out of water for long.
拜托 宝贝 你知道 自己不能长时间离开水
No, you promised me you'd move me into the tank above the bed.
不 你答应过我 会把我放进床上方的水族箱
Right, no. Of course, babe. A hunny percent.
没错 当然可以 宝贝 一定会的
I just got to, uh, you know, clear out the freshwater exotics first,
只不过 我得先清除淡水外来物种
and then it'll be all set.
然后就一切就绪
Oh, and I got a notes call with Shia
对了 我要跟希安开电话会议
on his new draft of Honey Boy 2. It's really starting to sing.
给他的新作《蜜糖男孩二》改剧本 肯定很精彩
Well, can I move in tomorrow?
那我明天可以搬进去吗?
Yeah, totally.
完全可以
Just like that, I'm supposed to pick up and leave?
你这么一说 我就得收拾东西离开?
Christmas in the desert. Terrific.
在沙漠里过圣诞节 太棒了
You're safer with Gen in Sedona, okay?
跟詹待在塞多纳你会更安全 好吗?
Some... things might happen soon.What do you mean?
可能 很快就有大事发生
What... what kind of things?
什么意思?什么事?
It's better you don't know.
你还是不知道的好
You call me out of the blue...I have called you
你突然打给我 几个星期以来
every day for weeks. This is the first time you've picked up.
我每天都给你打电话!今天你才接
You know, they kicked me out of the Tuesday Bible group.
他们不让我参加周二的圣经小组了
That has nothing to do with me.No?
与我无关 是吗?
Well, I heard Shelly whisper, "How the heck did Donna raise that girl?"
我听见雪莉低声说“唐娜怎么会养出那种女儿?”
Okay, just hit the road first thing tomorrow...
你明天一早出发就好
"That she would have an abortion?"
“她怎么做得出堕胎这种事?”
You're supposed to be held to a higher standard.
你应该达到更高的标准
That's how I raised you.
我是按高标准养育你的
Girls all over the world look up to you.
全世界的女孩以你为榜样
And now they think they can be loose, because there's no consequences...
现在她们认为自己可以为所欲为了 因为没有任何后果
That is none of your business,
那不关你的事
and it sure as fuck isn't Shelly's.
肯定也他妈的不关雪莉的事!
You're Starlight. You're a superhero.
你是星光 你是位超级英雄
I'm a person.
我是个人
Right now, none of that Starlight shit matters.
现在 星光之类的屁事已经不重要了
Then why did Hughie save the suit?
那休伊为什么留着你的战衣?
I am so, so sorry.
我非常 非常抱歉
That is so fucked.
真他妈糟透了
I pulled it from the trash.
我从垃圾桶里捡回来的
I mean, I thought you might regret tossing it someday.
以为某天你可能会后悔扔掉它
I don't even like looking at it.
我连看都不想看
Okay. All right.
好的 好吧
Done. I am... There it goes.
好了 我 这就扔掉
It is...
它
out of here.
滚蛋了
I just...
我只是
God. I just, I didn't...
天哪 我只是 不想
want to bring a baby into a world that's ending.
让宝宝降生到一个面临末日的世界
Hughie. It's just...
休伊 这种事
...it's just all too much.
这种事令人难以承受
I mean, there are so many fucking dumpster fires.
到处都一片混乱 情况失控
Where do we even start?
我们要从哪里入手呢?
We just take it step by step.
一步一步来吧
You smell like you've been drinking.
你一直在喝酒
I don't know what you want from me, all right?
我不知道你想怎样
I got here as fast as I could...I want you to do your fucking job.
我马上就赶来了 我希望你干好这一票
Whatever.
无所谓了
You really think this could be our Lee Harvey?
你真的认为他就是枪手?
That's what A-Train says. I say we visit him, too.
火车头说是他 要我说 我们也去会会他
Where the fuck you been?
你他妈的去哪了?
Shittin' a kidney.
蹲厕所里拉屎啊
All right, listen up.
好吧 听着
Now, don't get your knickers in a twist, but...
别不开心 但是
...you remember Neuman's dearly departed
你们还记得纽曼的心上人吧
virus bloke? Dr. Sameer Shah?
造病毒的那小子? 萨米尔沙阿博士?
I'm serious, Butcher. Don't.
我是认真的 布彻尔 别
Well, funny story.
有意思的是
Turns out he ain't that dead.
原来他还没死
He's been working for me, making some more of that virus.
他一直在为我工作 制造更多的病毒
What the fuck?
搞什么?
Wait, all they found was...
等等 他们只发现了
Goddamn it, you asshole.Did you cut off his leg?
天哪 你个混蛋 你砍断了他的腿?
All right, all right, keep your hair on.So, basically,
冷静点 你把人家截了肢
you've been amputatin' motherfuckers while working on a secret bioweapon,
让他研究秘密生物武器
and we're the ones that are supposed to chill?
却要我们冷静?
You are pissing away our best shot.
你会毁了我们最好的机会
Now, the trouble is, we've hit a slight snag.
问题是 我们遇到了一个小障碍
He can't make it deadly enough to top Homelander
如果病毒能干掉祖国人
without causing a, you know,global pandemic.
就会造成全球性的大瘟疫
Jesus.
天哪
Wait.
等等
Genocide.
种族灭绝
You're talking about Supe genocide. That's...
你说的是超人类的种族灭绝
Yeah, Butcher, even for you...
布彻尔 即使对你这种人来说 这也
Which is why I'm fucking telling you, innit?
所以我才告诉你们 不是吗?
You think I want that much blood on me hands?
你以为我想让双手沾满鲜血吗?
Yeah, you do. You want to fucking swim in it.
你想 你他妈的想在血海里游泳
No, I don't.
不 我不想!
No, I do not.
不 我不想
So, to keep the bug from burning through you lot like wildfire,
因此 为了防止病毒 像野火燎原一样灭了你们超人类
I thought ol' Sameer could do with
我觉得萨米尔需要一点帮助
a bit of a hand.From who?
谁的帮助?
A question both insightful and germane, my son.
真是极富有洞察力 与话题密切相关的问题 小子
Ah, here he is. Speak of the devil.
他来了 说曹操 曹操就到
Bonjour.
早上好
How the fuck did you get out?
你他妈的是怎么出狱的?
I had Mallory pull a few strings.
我让马洛里找了几个熟人
Just to be clear,
得说清楚
this was against my will.
这是违背我意愿的
I'd rather fuck a jar of fishing lures than to be free.
我宁愿操一罐鱼饵 也不想出狱
Oh, cool. Cool.
真不赖
All right, then.
好吧
Happy reunions. So,
重聚愉快
Frenchie will help sort the virus.
法兰奇会帮忙拣选病毒
We'll use it on Homelander and the VP and that's it, no one else.
只给祖国人和副总统注射病毒 其他人不会受影响
You fucking coward.
你个该死的胆小鬼
Okay, that works.
好的 这样可行
Kimiko, Frenchie, you two are on Dr. Shah.
喜美子 法兰奇 你们俩去帮沙阿博士
The rest of you, on the mystery man.
剩下的人去查那个神秘枪手
"Don't be a cunt."
“别做个混蛋”
Listen...You should... go on ahead.
听着 你应该 去
You what?
那你呢?
Without me. I gotta talk to Monique. It's...
我不去 我得和莫妮克谈谈 是
Oh, come off it.
得了吧
Don't leave me alone with this lot.
别让我独自面对这堆混球
Wait, what?
等等 怎么了?
He ain't going.You're not going? Why?
他不参与行动了不参与?为什么?
All right, so we gonna make this official?
我们要正式宣布?
Take a knee,I'll knight you with my dick.
跪下 我会用鸡巴封你为骑士
You're back in charge of The Boys again, all right?
你回来领导英雄克星 好吗?
I'm better off doing research anyway.
反正我还是做研究比较好
No, you can't do this.
不 你不能这样做
You don't got to do this.
你不必这样做
Yeah, he does. This is good for us.
他得这样做 这对我们有好处
You can't. Things are bad already
不行 这个混蛋不回来
without this fucking asshole back.
情况就已经很糟糕了
Look what I got to deal with.
这情况真难搞
Listen, it ain't a debate, you guys.
听着 这事无可争议 伙计们
I passed out.
我晕过去了
During a mission.
在执行任务期间
I ain't cut out to be skipper.
我不适合当头儿
But he is.
他才适合
So, it's him. It's you.
所以让他来当 你来当
End of story.
就这么办
Hey, come in, baby.
进来 宝贝
Okay, babe...
宝贝
Here, take this.
给 拿着
That's $10,000 cash.
一万美元现金
The rest of my accounts, I transferred into yours.
从我的账户转入你的名下
Marvin...
马文
Here's two one-way tickets to Belize.
这是两张去伯利兹的单程票
You and Janine's flights are tonight.
今晚你和珍妮的航班
Now, it's not forever,
只是待上一阵子
just until things blow over.Stop.
等情况平稳了就回来 停
Just stop.
停下来
Okay? Tell me what's wrong.
好吗?告诉我这是怎么回事
Something big's about to go down.
就要发生大事了
If we lose, shit's gonna get crazy.
如果我们输了 世界就会一团糟
If we win, shit's gonna get even crazier,
如果我们赢了 世界就更会是一团糟
so either way, y'all got to go.
所以 无论如何 你们都得走
And I'm sorry to make you have to pick up and leave again,
再次让你们收拾东西离开 我很抱歉
but I got one fucking job to do,
但我他妈的得完成任务
and that's to keep you and Janine safe,
这是为了保证你和珍妮的安全
and I'll be damned if I let any of this fucking sh...
我会良心受遣 如果我任由
I know how hard you try, Marvin,
我知道你很努力 马文
taking care of Janine and me.
照顾我和珍妮
Come with us.
跟我们走吧
I believe you.
我相信你
If you did all this, I...
如果你做了这些事 我
...I'm sure it's even worse than I'm imagining.
我确信情况比我想像的还糟
So let's go.
所以 我们走吧
The three of us, let's go be a family.
我们三个人 我们一家一起走
Monique...
莫妮克
you know that you and Janine are my heart,
你知道我最在乎你和珍妮
right?
对吧?
I can't.Look at you.
可我不能走 看看你
That panic attack was supposed to be a warning, Marvin.
那次恐慌发作本该是个警告 马文
Meet us at the airport...
在机场跟我们会合
...and this time tomorrow,
明天这个时候
baby, we'll be sipping rum punches
宝贝 我们就已经在海滩上喝着朗姆潘趣酒
on the beach while Janine dodges the waves.
看珍妮躲避海浪了
For over a decade, one man has been a voice you can trust.
纪念卡梅隆科尔曼 珍妮麦卡锡说:“又一位烈士离世”
And now that voice is gone.
现在 那个声音消逝了
Cameron Coleman has died of a brain aneurism
卡梅隆科尔曼因流感疫苗直接引起的
as a direct result of the flu vaccine.
脑动脉瘤去世
Gone from this world, but never gone from our hearts.
斯人已逝 永远铭记
Once again, tragedy...
再次报道
Hey. What happened to your assistant?Oh, Gregory? I fired him.
你的助理呢?格雷戈里?我解雇了他
Dumb fuck could never get my Sweetgreen order right.
总把我的沙拉订单搞错
What do you want?
你想干什么?
Listen. They know Cameron's not the leak...
听着 他们知道 卡梅隆不是泄密者了
Shut the fuck up. I don't want to hear that shit anymore.
闭嘴 我不想再听那些屁事了
You leave me the fuck out of that. I'm done.
你他妈的少扯上我 我不干了
You're shitfaced?
你喝醉了?
I am still the CEO of this company,
我仍然是这家公司的首席执行官
and if the CEO wants to get shitfaced at 11:00 a.m., I can.
如果首席执行官想在上午11点 喝个烂醉如泥 谁也管不了
He was the best.
他是最好的
He was the fucking best assistant I ever fucking had.
他是我最好的助手
And I fired him to get him away from this fucking place.
我解雇他 是为了让他离开这个该死的地方
I had Cameron killed. I had him killed.
我害卡梅隆被杀 是我陷害了他
Look, you saved my life.
你救了我的命
I could've done that some other way.
我本来可以用其他方式救你
He didn't have to die.
他不必死的
It's-it's so easy to become a monster around here.
在这里 很容易就会变成禽兽
What if we left? Huh?
我们当初离开会怎样呢?
You and me?
你和我?
I don't mean us fucking... ew, no.
我不是说发生性关系 真恶心 不是的
I spent my junior year abroad in Florence, we could just go, we could go.
我在佛罗伦萨上的大三 我们可以一走了之!
You have a passport.All right.
你有护照 好了
Oh, you don't need a passport. You just run...Hey, Ashley. Ashley.
你不需要护照 艾诗丽
Get your shit together.
你振作一点
Okay? You cannot be all wasted running your fucking mouth,
好吗?你不能烂醉如泥 口不择言
not when you have both of our lives in your fucking hands.
会害死我们俩的
Button it up.
管好你的嘴
Now.
现在
All right. I'll have a dekko around the back,
好了 我去后面看看
you two take the front, yeah?
你们俩去看看前面 好吗?
And then we'll pay the shooter a visit.
然后我们去找那个枪手
You know, I have been racking my brain...
我绞尽脑汁
trying to figure out when you got this soft spot for Supes.
想弄清楚你是什么时候 开始对超人类心软的
Was it when you shot your load and cream-pied Maeve?
是你跟梅芙翻云覆雨的时候吗?
All right, you know what?
好吧 知道吗?
Enough with the silent treatment, you stubborn prick,
受够你对我的沉默对待了 你个顽固不化的混蛋
I am done fucking around with you.
我们各走各路
See, I know you don't care about Starlight or Kimiko.
我知道你不在乎星光或喜美子
Not really. And Ryan?
并不真的在乎 莱恩呢?
He's not even yours.
他甚至都不是你的种
So, tell me...
所以 告诉我
what justifies the faith in the kid?
为什么对这孩子这么有信心?
I gave her my word.
我跟她保证过
Becca? Really?
贝嘉?真的吗?
If your love was so perfect and pure...
如果你的爱如此完美纯洁
...then why'd you fuck that waitress?
为什么还操那个女服务员?
I fucked up, all right.
我搞砸了 好吗?
And I quit the booze the next day, didn't I?
我第二天就戒了酒 不是吗?
Yeah.
是的
I can't help but notice you've been quitting the quitting lately.
不禁注意到你最近又开戒了
You know, you keep saying that you're doing all this to honor Becca's memory.
你一直说 做这一切都是为了纪念贝嘉
You never did that when she was alive.
她活着的时候 你没对她这么上心呀
So, don't you think it's time to cut the shit?
所以 你不觉得应该停止扯谎了吗?
Fuck off, cunt.
滚蛋吧 贱人
All clear.
没什么问题
Except for literal used tampons in the toilet.
不过 厕所里有用过的卫生棉条
Guys... Secret Service files.
伙计们 特勤局的文件
Detail assignments for January 6th.What?
1月6日的任务详情 什么?
It's a map of the D.C. Fairgrounds where Singer's having his rally.
华盛顿露天市场的地图 辛格尔要在那里举行集会
That's where they're giving him the old Dealey Plaza.
他们要在那里刺杀总统
M was right.
受保护者：当选总统罗伯特辛格尔 M说得没错
Oh, my God.
我的天哪!
Oh, thank God you're here.
谢天谢地 你们来了
He killed my husband.
他杀了我丈夫
He held me for days.
他关了我好几天了
Wait.
等等
Are you...?
你是
Yeah. Yeah, hi.
是的 我是 你好
Oh, my God. You are... burning up. Are you okay?
天哪 你身上好烫 你没事吧?
It's like a furnace in there.
里面热得像个熔炉好
Okay. Let's get you some help. Yeah?
我们找人帮你 好吗?
Come on.
来吧
Fuck! Stop!
他妈的!该死
Oi!
她划伤了我
What the fuck?So gross. Ugh!
什么东西?好恶心
Fuck!Do you see anything?No.
妈的!看到像她的人了吗?没有
Fucking Supe shapeshifters.
该死的变形超人类
I hate those cunts.
恨死那些贱人了
Got to hand it to Sage though...
不过不得不称赞智者
perfect choice for the job.
刺杀任务的完美人选
Wait, wait, wait. So we're saying that they could be anyone?
等等 所以 枪手变成什么样子都有可能?
How the fuck are we supposed to save the president
如果是这样
if the killer could be anyone?
我们怎么救总统?
By not shitting our panties.
不慌不忙地救
Hughie, wait a minute.
休伊 等一下
Oh, my God. You need stitches.
天哪 你得去缝针
I'll go to urgent care, okay?I'll go with you.
我会去急诊室 好吗?我陪你去
No, no, um, go back up there, get those plans before...
不 回公寓去 趁枪手回来之前
whoever gets back, all right? I'll catch up with you later.
拿到那些计划 好吗?我稍后再联系你
Okay. I love you.Love you.
好 我爱你 爱你
Printed-out boarding pass?
打印出来的登机牌?
Damn, what are you, 87?
你多大 87岁吗?
The fuck are you doing here?
你他妈的来这儿干什么?
You took the words right out of my mouth.
我正要问你呢
See, I ran by that shithole earlier.
我之前去了枪手那里
I saw Butcher, Hughie and Starlight going in.
我看到了布彻尔 休伊 星光
But one motherfucker was conspicuously absent.
但某个混蛋却没现身
So... this is it?
所以 你要一走了之?
You think I don't want to just peace out to Belize,
你以为我不想去伯利兹享清福
sip a daiquiri, smash the local talent?
喝杯代基里酒 找当地美女上床?
Get on Priceline then, motherfucker.
那就去买打折机票吧 混蛋嘿!
Hey. This shit ain't over.
这事还没完
It's over for me.
对我来说结束了
I've given enough.
我付出得够多了
Maybe I deserve to be fucking happy.
也许我他妈的值得去享享清福
You know, when I carried your ass to the ER,
我送你去急诊室时
there was a kid there.
看到一个孩子
His eyes were like...
他的眼神里充满敬畏
"Holy shit."
我的妈呀
Looking at me...
看着我
...like I was a hero.
好像我是位英雄
There were no screaming fans, no cameras.
没有尖叫的粉丝 没有摄像机
Nobody even knew.
甚至没有人知道
Except for this one kid.
除了这个孩子
That felt better than anything that I'd ever done at Vought.
那感觉比我在沃特 做过的所有事情都要美好
Because for once...
因为这一次
I didn't hate myself.
我没有讨厌自己
That's on you.
那要归功于你
A-Train, you don't get it, do you, man?
火车头 你不明白 是吗 伙计?
This fight that we're in?
我们参与的这场战斗
This never fucking ends.
他妈的永远不会结束
It killed my father. It killed his father.
它害死了我父亲 害死了我爷爷
And look at what it's doing to me.
看看它把我变成了什么样
It's tearing me the fuck apart.
让我痛苦不堪
Just like it did them.
重蹈我爸和我爷的覆辙
You know, I look in the mirror...
照镜子时
and I don't even see myself no more.
我再也认不出自己来了
I got nothing left.
我已经一无所有了
Except my family.
只有家人
You think Homelander and Vought...
你认为祖国人 沃特
...and all of this shit ain't coming to Belize?
还有这些烂事 不会影响到伯利兹吗?
This whole fucking world?
不会影响到整个世界?
Where's your family gonna go then?
那时 你的家人要去哪里?
Thanks.
谢谢
After you eat,
等你吃完
we'll adjust your centrifugation numbers.
我们再调整离心次数
I think peut-etre we should try a glycerol gradient.
我想 也许 我们应该尝试甘油梯度
This, uh...quote-unquote "lab" can't produce what he wants.
这个“实验室”无法制造出他想要的东西
What we all want.
是我们都想要的东西
Homelander... fini, do we not?
我们都想干掉祖国人 不是吗?
You know, you worked in the finest lab with the best equipment,
你在最好的实验室工作过 那里拥有最好的设备
but moi?
可我呢?
I have worked in filthy basements with equipment
我曾在肮脏的地下室里工作过
from dumpsters and dollar stores.
用的是从垃圾箱和一元店淘来的设备
Necessity is the MILF of invention.
必要性是促成发明的第一要素
You know, um, he would talk to people who weren't here.
知道嘛 他对着空气说话
Your friend.
你的那位朋友
Some music, perhaps?
或许可以听点音乐?
I noticed you enjoy truly revolting garbage from the 1990s.
我注意到你很享受20世纪90年代 令人反感的垃圾音乐
Help you work.Bon appetit.
帮你工作 祝你胃口大开
This virus.
这种病毒
It's just for Homelander, right? Not for Vicky?
只给祖国人用 对吧? 不会用在维琪身上?
Ryan, it's Dad.
莱恩 是爸爸
Hey, listen, buddy, I-I'm sorry I've been so busy lately,
听着 儿子 最近太忙了 我很抱歉
but I hear you're having some issues
但我听说你不大同意拍那个
with the-the puppet show thing.
布偶戏的节目
Um, look, I got a lot going on here,
我手头上事情很多
buddy, so, uh, do me a favor,
儿子 所以 帮我个忙 不要抱怨
just-just-just suck it up and-and do it, all right? For me.
拍就是了 好吗?为了我
Terrific. Love you. Great. Bye.
太好了 爱你 很好 再见
Are you absolutely sure
你绝对确定
that he is the leak?
他就是泄密者?
The little shit broke wide open. He confessed to everything.
那小混球都招了 什么都承认了
Sir.Webweaver.
先生 网络喷子
Ew, what the fuck?
搞什么?
Ew.I'm sorry.
对不起
Happens when I'm nervous.
我一紧张就这样
Oh, fuck.Ain't got to be nervous, just...
不用紧张 说吧
go on, tell him what you told me. I know.
告诉他你跟我说过的话 我知道
Yes, ma'am.
是 女士
Yes, sir.
是 先生
Whatever you want to know.
我知无不言
How does it work?
怎么运作的?
There's a hole in the suit so the webs can get out...
战衣上有个洞 网就可以喷出去
No. No. How does it work with William Butcher?
不 跟威廉布彻尔是怎么运作的?
Yeah, well, uh... He-he...
这个嘛 他
he comes to me.
来找我
I tell him what he wants to know.
我告诉他 他想知道的事情
Oh, for God sakes.
老天爷呀
That's just embarrassing.Just shut the fuck up.
真令人尴尬 他妈的闭嘴吧
Now, one of Butcher's crew
布彻尔的一名下属穿着你
was wearing your nasty-ass suit to Tek-Knight's.
令人作呕的战衣去了泰克骑士的庄园
Did you give it to them?
战衣是你给他的吗?
I'm not proud of it.
我万分羞愧
There it is.
看吧
Help me out with something here.
帮我搞清楚一件事
Few weeks back,
在那之前的几周
how did you know where I was meeting Victoria Neuman?
你怎么知道 我在哪里见维多利亚纽曼?
Look, I-I messed up. I know, I know...
听着 我搞砸了 我知道
I'm sorry.
对不起
I...
我
I... I don't feel very good.
我感觉很难受
You ever meet this British guy?
但你见过这个英国人吧?
He's a liar.Hmm.
他是个骗子
He fucks with your brain.
把人搞得精神崩溃
Feeble brains, maybe.Yes.
也许是你意志薄弱 是的
Feeble. I'm all fucked up.
薄弱 我脑子进水了
I screwed you.
我给您制造了麻烦
I'm so, so sorry.
我非常 非常抱歉
I'll make you proud. I swear to God.
我会让您感到骄傲的 我向上帝发誓
Oh, buddy, what am I gonna do with you?
伙计 我拿你怎么办呢?
Jesus.Oh, stop.
天哪 别拉了
Wait, wait!
等等 等等
What?It wasn't me.
什么?不是我干的
No, please.
求你了!
Thank you, Firecracker.
谢谢你 鞭炮
You bet.
没问题
For Noel.It's not much.
圣诞快乐 一份小小心意
I've missed you.
我很想念你
I came every day. You wouldn't see me.
我每天都去 可你不肯见我
I was ashamed.
我很惭愧
For what you did to Colin and his family.
因为你对科林和他家人所做的一切
You told a lot to Annie. The rest I pieced together.
你向安妮倾诉了很多 其余的都是我拼凑起来的
Then you know why I had to turn myself in.
那你就知道我为什么要自首了
You're exhausting.
你累了
Sorry.
对不起
You always do this. All moody.
你总是这样 喜怒无常
Torturing yourself.
折磨自己
What else was I supposed to do?
不然我该怎样?
Ask for help. Come to me for help.
寻求帮助 找我帮你
You can't help.You don't understand.
你无能为力 你不理解
Do you know why I can't speak?
你知道我为什么不能说话吗?
You watched Shining Light kill your parents.
你看着闪光军杀了亲生父母
Your brother told me.
你弟弟告诉我的
I never told Kenji the truth.
我从来没有告诉健二真相
It was my first night at the camp.
我在营地的第一个晚上
We move like ghosts.
我们像幽灵一样移动
In silence.
寂静无声
So will you.
你们也一样
So the first girl to cry out?
第一个哭出来的女孩
She loses.
就输了
You ready?
准备好了吗?
I murdered her without making a sound.
我无声无息地杀了她
Then when I was allowed to speak again...
后来允许我说话了
I couldn't.
可我说不出来了
You did not have a choice.
当时你别无选择
Of course I did.
我当然有选择
Better they kill me, than what I did to that girl.
让他们杀了我 总比我对那个女孩做的事强
What I did to lots of girls.
比我对很多女孩做的事都强
I look in the mirror and hate what I see.
我看着镜子里的自己 感到无比厌恶
So I understand,
所以我比你想像的
more than you know.
更理解你的感受
You should not hate yourself.
你不应该恨自己
Then neither should you.
那你也不应该
How can we possibly forgive ourselves?
我们怎么可能原谅自己?
How can we move on?
我们怎样才能继续活下去?
When the virus is ready, we should set him free, no?
病毒准备就绪时 我们应该释放他 不是吗?
Butcher won't be happy.
布彻尔会不高兴的
Then it must be the right thing to do.
那这一定是正确的做法
Babe, that you?
宝贝 是你吗?
Yeah, babe.
是的 宝贝
Can you pick me up some Sugarfish?
你能给我买些生鱼片吗?
No. We've talked about this.
不行 我们已经讨论过这事了
I can't take part in the slaughter of albacore.
我不能参与屠杀长鳍金枪鱼
One of my ride-or-dies is an albacore.
我有个最好的朋友就是长鳍金枪鱼
Okay, so I don't get to stay where I want
好吧 所以我既不能待在想待的地方
or eat what I want.
也不能吃想吃的东西
What's that supposed to mean?
这话什么意思?
"Sometimes the way you get them is the way you lose them."
“有时 怎样获得就怎样失去”
Why are you quoting Lisa Vanderpump?
为什么引用丽莎范德庞普的话?
I know about Sage.
我知道智者的事
What are you talking about? Sage?
说什么呢 智者?
Don't patronize me, Kevin. I've known for a while.
别以为假装对我好 就能瞒天过海 凯文
My suckers can smell her on you
我已经知道一段时间了
after your trysts.
你们幽会之后 在你身上
Like the one you're coming from now.
我的吸盘能感受到她的味道 就像现在这样
I love you so much.
我真的很爱你
Your gentle heart, your fearless writing.
你温柔的心 你无畏的写作
Can you honestly say she feels the same?
你能诚实地说她像我一样爱你吗?
Look, I don't know what to tell you right now.
我现在不知道该怎么跟你说
Try the truth.
试着说实话
It's not too late.
还不算太晚
This is worth fighting for.
这份爱值得为之奋斗
We're worth fighting for.
我们的爱值得为之奋斗
There's no way Sage cares about you the way that I do.
智者根本不可能像我这么关心你
She says that I'm a superior being,
她说我是高人一等的生物!
and she has four limbs.
她是人类
That is not fair.
这不公平!
Yeah, well, it is what it is.
情况如此 无可奈何
That's a dumb, nothing phrase,
这是句愚蠢 空洞的话
spoken by...Dumb people?
说这话的是 愚蠢的人?
Dumb people? I hate it when you get nasty.
愚蠢的人?你残酷无情时令我讨厌
Well, what choice do I have, when you're rubbing my face in it?
我有什么选择?谈敏感问题时 你根本不顾及我的感受
Oh, what, that I'm happy for once?!
我享乐一次 有什么大不了的?
I'm sorry!I feel sorry for you.
对不起 我为你感到遗憾
For me? For me? Look at you.
为我感到遗憾?看看你那副德行
You won't be laughing when you realize she doesn't respect you.
你意识到她并不尊重你时就不会笑了
She does respect me!
但她确实尊重我!
Wake up, Kevin. She's using you.
醒醒吧 凯文 她在利用你
You shut the fuck up!You're throwing us away for a woman
闭嘴!你正在为了一个认为你很可悲的女人
who thinks you're pathetic...
损耗我们的感情
Kevin! Kevin!
凯文!凯文!
Come back!
回来
Please, Kevin, please.
求你了 凯文!求你了
Please, Kevin.
求你了 凯文
Kevin, I-I-I can't breathe.
凯文 我 我无法呼吸
Please...What?
求你 什么?
Oh, my God.Kevin!
天哪凯文
Please!
求你了!
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
他妈的
Kevin!
凯文!
Open the door!Fuck.
开门!妈的!
I love... you.
我爱 你
Okay.
好
Deep? Deep?
喂 深海 深海?
Did you get all that?Yes, sir.
你都明白了吗?是的 先生
I finally have clarity now.
我现在终于清楚了
Good.
好的
I will kill whoever you want me to kill, whenever you want me to kill them.
你想杀谁 我就去杀 随时听你派遣
I'll kill every goddamn fish in the ocean if you say so.
你一声令下 我就会杀死海洋里所有该死的鱼
Okay.
好
Attaboy. Um...
好样的
Well, get to it.
去做吧
Madam Vice President-elect?Yeah?
当选副总统女士?在呢
There's someone here to see you.
有人来见您
Fuck, I'm gonna miss New York bodegas.
我会很想念纽约的杂货店
Listen, we need to talk.
听着 我们需要谈谈
You can still stop all this, all right? Just stop.
你仍然可以阻止这一切 罢手吧
You must be pretty desperate if you're throwing a Hail Mary like this. Jesus...
想让我改变主意 你肯定是黔驴技穷了
Five minutes, all right? Just five minutes
五分钟 可以吗?
where we cut the bullshit and we talk, just you and me,
不说废话 我们俩好好谈谈
about how fucked all this is.
情况有多么糟糕
What it is, is politics. You know how it goes,
这是政治 你知道的
strange bedfellows.
为达目的求同存异罢了
Yeah, but it's not like you're palling around with Mitt Romney.
这可不是在跟米特罗姆尼合作
You're working with Homelander.
你在跟祖国人合作!
He's gonna kill the president.
他要刺杀总统
That sounds fucking insane coming out of my mouth.
这话从我嘴里说出来 听起来难以置信
And when Homelander chucks all the Starlighters
祖国人把星光追随者们
into internment camps, you're just,
都关进拘留营
you're cool with that, too?
你也觉得无所谓吗?
You didn't know about the camps.
你对拘留营一无所知
Why do you think that you were at Tek-Knight's?
你觉得为什么自己 被请到了泰克骑士庄园?
That's what his prisons are for.I got to get back to it.
要用他的监狱做拘留营 我得接着打包了
I still have all the dirt on you. What you said at Tek-Knight's.
我手上还有对你不利的证据 你在泰克骑士庄园里说的话
Everything.
每一个字
Is that a threat?
这是威胁吗?
No.
不是
Because when we drop it, then you'll kill us all.
因为我们一发布 你就会杀了我们所有人
Like you said, mutually assured destruction.
像你说的 肯定会两败俱伤
But it doesn't have to be that way.
但并非一定要两败俱伤
And if you're even, like, one percent of the person that I knew,
如果你还尚存一丝人性 就像从前的你
then I don't think you really want to do this.
那么 我认为你并不想这样做
You can still step back.
你还来得及罢手
Vic, it's not too late.
维琪 现在还不算太晚
Thanks for coming by.
感谢你过来见我
I'm sorry...
你父亲的事
...to hear about your dad.
我很遗憾
Hughie's still not answering. I'm worried about him.
休伊还是不接电话 我很担心他
Sup, cum burgers?
还好吗 小可爱?
The fuck you doing here?
你他妈的怎么来了?
Homelander is sick of your shit, bro.
祖国人受够你了 兄弟
Said to put you out of your misery.
说要帮你脱离苦海
And he sent you?
所以派了你来?
Sure you ain't too busy tongue lashing your octo-pussy?
看来给章鱼舔屄还不够你忙的
What? No. I never...
才没有 我从没
He didn't just send me.
他不光派了我来
Do you know what?
知道吗?
I can't believe I'm saying this,
我不敢相信自己会说这种话
but it's Christmas.
但现在是圣诞节
You two twats leg it right now,
你们两个笨蛋赶快逃吧
and we'll forget you was ever here.
我们会忘记你们来过这里什么
What, dude? I can barely understand you,
伙计?我几乎听不懂你说话
your accent's insane.What the fuck do you want, Deep?
你的口音太重了 你到底想要怎样 深海?
Justice, you fucking bitch.
讨个正义 你个婊子
God, I'm gonna enjoy this so much.
天哪 我会非常享受杀掉你
First, you tried to cancel me,
首先 你想害我被封杀
victimize an innocent man because I guess
陷害我这个无辜者
that's just cool to do to white guys nowadays.
因为现在 这样对待白人男性会显得很酷
But joke's on you. #MeToo's over,
结果你自食其果 “我也是”
sweetheart, it didn't work.
反性骚扰运动已经终结了 毫无结果
I do not respect your truth.
我觉得你说的并不是真相
I do not honor and cherish your story.
我不尊重 也不珍惜你的故事
And I do not fucking apologize.
我他妈的才不会道歉呢
Cunt's narcoleptic.
这傻逼有嗜睡症
Kessler,
凯斯勒
whatever you did to Ezekiel,
无论你对以西结做了什么
do it again.
再做一遍
What are you doing?
你在干什么?
Wait, are you... You're the leak?
等等 你是泄密者?
Did he just talk?
他说话了?
Bro, it was you, bro?
兄弟?是你吗 兄弟?
Deep, just FYI, I have always,
深海 告诉你一声 我一直
always fucking hated your ass.
一直都很讨厌你
Fuck, he can fly?
他妈的 你会飞?
Eat a flying dick, motherfuck...
叫你好看 傻
Noir will be back up here in no time, so let's go.
玄色很快就回来了 我们快走吧
He's right fucking there. Let's do him.
他就在这儿 我们干掉他吧
You know how, Butcher? 'Cause I don't,
你知道怎么干掉他吗 布彻尔? 我可不知道
but Noir sure as hell's gonna know how to fucking kill us.
但玄色肯定知道怎么干掉我们
Now, come the fuck on.
所以 是快走吧
Alexa, play "Dave Matthews Chill Mix."
亚莉克莎 播放戴夫马修斯的
Playing Dave Matthews...Alexa, please fucking don't.
平静混音音乐 亚莉克莎 求你别播火车头
What the fuck, A-Train?
搞什么?
Listen, we got to go, now.
听着 我们得走了 现在就走
Deep and Noir know that I'm the leak.
深海和玄色知道我是泄密者了 等等
Wait, what?Homelander's about to find out any second.
什么?祖国人很快就会知道该死的混蛋
Did you say anything about me, you fucking asshole?
你有说过我的事吗?
No, of course not. I didn't say anything.
当然没有 我什么也没说
A-Train, what the fuck? What the fuck?Ashley.
火车头 搞什么?艾诗丽
This is our chance. This is our chance.
这是我们的机会 失不再来
Florence, anywhere,
佛罗伦萨 哪里都行
but let's go.
但我们这就得走
I can't.
我不能走
Suit yourself.Wait, wait.
那你自便吧 等等
Your chip.
你的芯片
Don't forget to cut it out.
别忘了把它取出来
Hi, sorry, you're Starlight, right?
不好意思 你是星光 对吧?
Oh, um...Can I just get a selfie?
我可以拍张自拍吗?好的
Oh, that's a good one.
拍得很好
Okay. Thank you.Thanks.
好 谢谢 谢谢
So what's it gonna be, M?
要怎么办 M?
You gonna help us stop an assassination, a violent insurrection?
你要帮我们阻止暗杀和暴力叛乱?
Or you off to have a wank?
还是说会置之不理?
Looks like a wank then.
看来是要置之不理
Who's Kessler?
凯斯勒是谁?
Kessler?In the Flatiron.
凯斯勒?在办公室大楼里
You shouted a name, "Kessler,"
你喊了一个名字“凯斯勒”
and something that had to do with Ezekiel.
说了些跟以西结有关的事情
What was that?
那是怎么回事?
No idea what you're on about there, luv.Hmm.
不知道你在说些什么 亲爱的
You're really not coming.
你真的不来了
Those rum punches are gonna have to wait, babe.
只好以后再喝朗姆潘趣酒了 宝贝
Janine needs you.
珍妮需要你
Monique, the one thing I've wanted more than anything,
亲爱的 我别无所求 只有一个目标
my one prayer every night,
我每晚都祈祷它会实现
has been to be with you and Janine again.
就是再次跟你和珍妮
To be a family.
成为一家人
But if I'm gonna protect you two the way I have to,
但如果我不得不这样保护你们俩
I can't.
我就无法实现这个目标
I just...
我就
Maybe one day.
也许某天会实现
"Maybe"? What the hell's that supposed to mean, Marvin? Maybe?
也许?“也许”是什么意思 马文?
I got to go, babe.Marvin, wait...
我得挂了 宝贝马文 等等
Homelander?
祖国人?
Are you all right?
你没事吧?
A-Train?
火车头?
I'm so...How could he do this to me?
他怎么可以这样对我?
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉
You know, some folks are just...
你知道 有些人就是
...well, they're born uppity.
他们生来就傲慢自负
Where is he?
他在哪里?
He cut out his tracking chip.
他取出了追踪芯片
And his family's gone, too.
他的家人也消失了
Of course.
当然
You sent Deep and Noir after Butcher?
你派了深海和玄色去杀布彻尔?
We talked about this.
我们讨论过这事
Smartest person in the world,
世界上最聪明的人
and you didn't know A-Train was the leak?
却不知道火车头是泄密者?
I knew.
我知道
You knew.
你知道
And you let us kill Webweaver for nothing?
却让我们无缘无故地杀死网络喷子?
Oh, shit.
妈的
You killed Webweaver?
你们杀了网络喷子?
Did you think he was the leak?
你们以为他是泄密者?
He was a junkie who'd confess to nailing Christ on the cross
他这个瘾君子 只要能让他回家接着吸毒
if it got him home for his next fix.
把基督钉在十字架上这种事 他都会承认
I was very clear.
我说得很清楚
No more secrets.
别再隐藏秘密了
But A-Train only leaked
但火车头只是泄露了
exactly the information I wanted Butcher and his team to know.
我想让布彻尔及其团队知道的信息
He was the perfect misinformation delivery system.Until now.
在此之前 他一直都是传递错误信息的完美人选
This was all part of the plan.
这都是计划的一部分
Okay.
好吧
Get the fuck out of here. You're done.
滚吧 你走人吧
Go back to your little litter box in Detroit
回到你在底特律的小垃圾公寓里
and die alone.
孤独地死去吧
You promised.
你答应过我的
You promised me you would listen to me.
你答应过我你会听我的
You're lucky I'm not sending you home in a bucket.
我没把你大卸八块寄回家 已经算你走运了
Go.
滚
Fine, surround yourself with people like her.
好吧 身边只留下她这种人
Then you can systematically eliminate anyone who gets in your way,
你可以系统地消除任何妨碍你的人
but there's one person you will never, ever defeat.
但有一个人 你永远无法打败
Good luck without me.
没了我 祝你好运
We don't need her.
我们不需要她
Just-just get out.
出去
Are you sure there's...
你确定
...nothing I can...do for you?
没有我能为你做的事吗?
No.
确定
Oh, just get the fuck out.Okay. Mm-hmm.
快滚出去吧 好
Bro?
兄弟
Bro!
兄弟!
Bro.
兄弟
Hey, you.
你好呀
Hey, so we've had a day.
我们今天很不顺
Wait, what's the rush?
等等 急什么?
Homelander. He fired me.
祖国人 他解雇了我
Wait, but you can't leave. I love you.
等等 但你不能离开 我爱你
We have something special, don't we?Wait.
我们有真感情 不是吗?等等
Is she lobotomizing herself to fuck you, too?
她对自己进行脑白质切除术后 也操你吗?
What do you mean, "lobotomizing herself"?
她没做什么脑白质切除术啊
Bro.
兄弟
You were right. It's ready.
你是对的 准备好了
The glycerol gradient.
甘油梯度
Uh, it worked.Even in a shitty lab.
即使在一个破烂的实验室里也有效
After we do an FFA test,
进行眼底萤光素血管造影测试后
see that the virus is working,
如果病毒发挥作用
we have some good news for you, mon ami.
我们就要告诉你个好消息 我的朋友
No!
不
Kimiko.
喜美子
Okay.
没关系
Mon coeur, look at me.
心肝 看着我
Take this. Focus on this.
抓住这个 专心看这个
I'm sorry!
对不起!
It's okay.
没关系
Yeah. You're okay.
嘿 你没事
You didn't twig to what Sameer was up to?
而你却没有意识到萨米尔想跑?
Well, with bindings so thick, he must have worked them for days.
被锁得那么牢 他一定是已经准备了好几天
Maybe weeks. No?All right. All right.
也许好几周 不是吗?好吧
What matters is if Sameer can get the bug out of a sheep's head,
重要的是 如果萨米尔能从死羊身上提取出病毒
Frenchie can get it out of Kimiko's gam.
法兰奇就可以 从喜美子的断腿里提取出病毒
All right, so, we know the virus works,
我们知道病毒是有效的
but is it strong enough?To kill Homelander?
但它足够强大吗?足以杀死祖国人吗?
No. But to kill Neuman at least?
杀不死 但杀死纽曼?
C'est possible.
是有可能的
We've been on this for weeks, and all we have is a maybe?
好几个星期了 结果只是个“可能”?
Yo...
各位
Why all the grim faces?
为什么都板着脸?
We've done more with less.
以前比这糟糕 但我们都挺过来了
Ain't nobody gonna murk the president, not on our fuckin' watch.
我们绝不容许任何人暗杀总统
Frenchie, that virus...it ain't gonna cook itself, brother.
法兰奇 病毒不会凭空出现 兄弟
All right, let's go.
开工啦
Chop, chop, motherfuckers.
快点 混蛋们
Ryan, it's Dad.
莱恩 是爸爸
Hey, listen, buddy, I-I'm sorry I've been so busy lately,
听着 儿子 最近太忙了 我很抱歉
but I hear you're having some issues with the-the puppet show thing.
但我听说你不大同意拍那个 布偶戏的节目
Um, look, I got a lot going on here, buddy, so, uh, do me a favor.
我手头上事情很多 儿子 所以
Just-just suck it up and-and do it.
帮我个忙 不要抱怨 拍就是了
All right? For me. Terrific. Love you. Great. Bye.
好吗?为了我 太好了 爱你 很好 再见
There he is.
他来了
Where the fuck were you when I needed you?
我需要你的时候 你他妈的在哪里?
Silent treatment goes both ways.
沉默对待是双向的
Stop. Stop. Just stop.
停下来 快停下来
This song isn't cool.
这首歌不行
Honestly, none of this is cool.
老实说 这些都不行
Go to fucking commercial!
快他妈的切广告
No. Don't go to commercial.
不 不要切广告
Keep rolling, please.
继续拍 拜托了
Your family isn't your enemy.
你的家人不是敌人
Your family is all you've got.
你的家人是你的全部
I've been thinking about my mom a lot lately.
最近我总在想我妈
She died.
她死了
But she loved Christmas.
但她很喜欢圣诞节
And s'mores with Reese's.
喜欢用锐滋糖果做的棉花糖夹心饼干
And Terms of Endearment.
喜欢看《母女情深》
And she loved her husband Billy.
她爱自己的丈夫比利
But she wouldn't love this.
但她不会喜欢这个布偶节目
She wouldn't want me doing it.
她不会希望我拍这个
My mom always told me to tell the truth...
我妈总是告诉我要说实话
...which is why...
因此
I'm sorry.
对不起
And that...
这就是为何
...is why I got faith in the kid,
我对这孩子充满信心
you little fucking beauty.
太他妈的让我骄傲了
Wanker.
混蛋
Call 911!
打911!
Hey, Annie?
安妮?
I, uh... I didn't actually go to urgent care today.
其实 我今天没去急诊室
Yeah, I could tell.
我看得出来
Yeah. Well, I... I went to go see Vicky.
是的 我去找维琪了
Hughie!Yeah, look, I know it...
休伊 我知道 那样做
I'm okay. It's just...
我没事 只是
I don't know. I thought maybe I could talk her out of it, or...
我不知道 我想也许 自己可以说服她罢手 或者
And...?
结果呢?
what made you...
是什么让你
I-I... just thought I would... try it on.
我只是想试试
Okay. How-How's it... feel?
好吧 感觉怎么样?
Feels annoying...
感觉很烦人
that you were right.
因为你是对的
We'll take it... step by step,
我们一步一步来
one dumpster fire at a time.
一次处理一个麻烦
So, you're saying, I give genius advice.
所以 你是说我给出了天才的建议
Don't push it.
别太得意了
Now...
现在
admit it.
承认吧
You have fantasized
你留下战衣时
about... keeping this suit on for this.
幻想过这一幕
I haven't...not fantasized about it.
我并非没有幻想过